A Finding Aid to the Charles Rand Penney Papers, 1923-1994, bulk 1945-1994, in the Archives of American Art AAA.pennchar
Archives of American Art
- Art Collection Files, 1923-1994; Series 1; 22.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-23, OV 24
  - Miro, Joan (Box 15)
    - Albert White Gallery, 1973-1982 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1974-1987 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Arnold Herstand and Company, circa 1980s (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Art Gallery of Ontario, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Artist at 87, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Chicago, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Centenary Exhibitions, Barcelona, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Death of the Artist, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Donald Morris Gallery, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Elkon Gallery, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Gallery Maeght, Fondation Maeght, 1979-1990 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Gallery Moos Limited, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Goldman Art Publishers, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Guggenheim Museum, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Martin Gordon Gallery, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1970-1993 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Nathan Silberberg Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1961-1986 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Pace Gallery, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Periodical, "Miro, A Conversation", Arts Canada Journal (1980-1981) (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Periodical, "Conversation with Miro", Art News (1980) (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Perls Galleries, 1970-1982 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Pierre Matisse Gallery, 1967-1986 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - St. James Park au Crepuscule (1958), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Untitled, Pencil and Watercolor, 1961-1992 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Weintraub Gallery, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 15)
    - General, 1967-1989 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Clippings, 1959-1976 (Box 15, Folder 63-64)
    - Clippings, 1977-1988 (Box 15, Folder 65-66)
    - Columbus Museum of Art, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Death of the Artist, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - "Henry Moore: 60 Years of His Art" (1983) (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Fischer Fine Art Limited, London, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Franklin Mint Almanac, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Hirschhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden Collection, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Memorial Art Gallery, circa 1980s (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 16)
    - M. Knoedler and Co. Inc. and Harry A. Brooks, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Nan Miller Gallery Exhibitions (1986-1987) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - New York City Exhibitions (1970) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Photographic Material, Moore's Visit to Ago, Toronto, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Post Cards and Greeting Cards, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Poster, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Reclining Female Figure (1945-1946), circa 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Shelter-Sketch-Book (1940-1942), circa 1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Tasende Gallery, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Thomas Gibson Fine Art Limited, London, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Toronto, Art Gallery of Ontario, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Toronto, Clippings, 1965-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Toronto, Henry Moore Sculpture Center, 1966-1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Toronto, Post Cards, circa 1960s (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Upright Motives, Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Upright Motive #5 (1955-1956), 1964-1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Upright Motive #5 (1955-1956), Corrosion, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Upright Motives #5 and #8 (1955-1956), Article, 1966-1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Upright Motives #5 and #8 (1955-1956), Correspondence Regarding David Finn's 39 Photographs, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Upright Motive #8 (1955-1956), 1964-1986 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Upright Motive Maquette for #13, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Weintraub Gallery, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Morris, Robert, 1970-1994 (Box 16, Folder 24-25)
  - Motherwell, Robert, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Munakata, Shiko, 1960-1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Myers, Jerome, 1972-1985 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Nadelman, Elie, 1971-1994 (Box 16, Folder 29-30)
  - Nakashima, George, 1982-1994 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Nakian, Reuben (Box 16)
    - General, 1980-1991 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - D. Laurenti Gallery, 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Europa + The Bull (circa 1958), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Gruenebaum Gallery, 1973-1983 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Rhode Island School of Design, President's Fellows Award, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Neujean, Nathaniel, 1968-1986 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Nevelson, Louise (Box 16)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Articles and Publicity, 1968-1994 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Nevelson, Louise (Box 17)
    - Articles and Publicity, 1968-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
    - Artist at 70, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Conversation with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Regarding Art in Penney's Collection, 1968-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Death of the Artist, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Dunkelman Gallery, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Hokin Gallery, Inc., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - New York State Governor's Arts Award, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Pace Gallery, 1971-1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Periodical, Time, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Noguchi, Isamu (Box 17)
    - General, 1968-1992 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Arnold Herstand and Co., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Articles, 1979-1989 (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
    - Artist at 75, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Billy Rose Art Garden, Israel Museum, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - "Bronze and Iron Sculpture" (1988) (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Calligraphics (1957), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Conversation with Hugh Hardy (1980), circa 1980s (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence Regarding Catalog of Complete Works, 1979-1987 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Death of the Artist, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Governor Nelson A. Rockafeller Empire State Plaza Art Collection, circa 1980 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Isamu Noguchi Garden Museum, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Lunar (1968), 1969-1993 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - National Medal of Art Award, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Noguchi Table (1944), 1988-1992 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Pace Gallery, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Portrait Sculptures, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - The Queen (1931), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Rudder Table, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Sculpture Retrospective (1968) (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - "Seven Stones" (1986) (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - U.S. Pavilion at 42nd Venice Biennale, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Victim (1962), 1968-1991 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Ogden, Sam, 1969-1982 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Okazaki, Kazuo, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, 1967-1994 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Oldenberg, Claes, 1967-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Ortman, George, 1965-1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Pallas, Jim, 1965-1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Parker, Robert Andrew (Box 18)
    - General, 1963-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Lecture, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - A Bird (1958), 1961-1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Information, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - The Cruiser Drottwing Victoria (1954), 1962-1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - G Contemporary Paintings Gallery, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Guggenheim Grant Recipient, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Periodical, Fortune, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Periodical, Playboy Magazine Illustration, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Schuman Gallery, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Terry Dintenfass Gallery, 1966-1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - World House Galleries, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Pearlstein, Philip (Box 18)
    - General, 1969-1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Allan Frumkin Gallery, 1969-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Article, "The Prints of Philip Pearlstein" by Dennis Adrian, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Associated American Artists, 1970-1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Brooke Alexander, Inc., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Clark Polak's Gallery, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Donald Morris Gallery, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Fendrick Gallery, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Finch College Museum of Art, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Gallery 169, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Gimpel Fils, 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Hirschl and Adler Modern, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Landfall Press, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - National Academy of Design, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Nude with One Leg Raised (1968), circa 1970 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - "Philip Pearlstein: A Retrospective" (1983) (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Wilson Arts Center/The Harley School, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Pepper, Beverly (Box 18)
    - General, 1969-1988 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1975-1992 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Baumgartner Galleries, Inc., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Black Paul (1969), 1969-1987 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Blue, Silver, and Yellow (1968), 1969-1987 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Buffalo Subway Art, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Charles Cowles Gallery, Inc., 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Colonna Triano, Colonna Aventinus, Colonna Martius, Colonna Senatoria (1979), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1994 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Curtis Bill Pepper, Husband, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Gerald Peters Gallery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - The Glamour Magazine After Five Cookbook (1952), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - International Sculpture Center, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - James Corcoran Gallery, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Maxi Zig Zag, Dedication at Buffalo Convention Center, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Nina Freudenheim Gallery, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - "No Man's Land" (1990), Socrates Sculpture Park (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Penney's 1972 Christmas Card (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Penney's 1988 Christmas Card, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Periodical, Art News, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - "Sculpture in Place" (1986), 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Slides of Installation at Memorial Art Gallery, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Studio Marconi, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Ventaglia #671 (1967), 1967-1987 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Vertical Ventaglio (1967-1968), At Olcott, 1969-1987 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Vertical Ventaglio (1967-1968), Conservation by Memorial Art Gallery in 1987, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Vertical Ventaglio (1967-1968), Gift to Memorial Art Gallery, 1977-1989 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Vertical Ventaglio (1967-1968), Loan to Indianapolis Museum of Art in 1972-1973, 1962-1987 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Zig Zag (1967), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Pereira, I. Rice, 1964-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Picasso, Pablo (Box 19)
    - General, 1961-1971 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
    - General, 1972-1980 (Box 19, Folder 4-6)
    - General, 1981-1986 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
    - Retrospective Exhibition at Museum of Modern Art (1980) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - "The Sketchbooks of Picasso" (1986) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Pissarro, Camille, 1970-1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Pollock, Jackson (Box 19)
    - General, 1978-1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Betty Parsons, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Catalogue Raisonne, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Clement Greenberg, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - East Hampton, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Lee Krasner Pollock, Wife, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Marlborough Gallery, Inc., 1982 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Samuel M. Kootz, Art Dealer, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - University of Iowa, 1976-1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Untitled (1941), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Untitled (circa 1950), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Works Progress Administration, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Ponce de Leon, Michael, 1964-1985 (Box 19, Folder 27-28)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard, 1984-1992 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Pozzatti, Rudy O., 1964-1970 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Ray, Man, 1969-1994 (Box 19, Folder 31-32)
  - Rehn, Frank Knox Morton, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Renteria, Philip, 1976-1983 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Richier, Germaine, Figure in Landscape (1954), 1978-1985 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Richier, Germaine, Foret (1952), 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Rickey, George (Box 20)
    - General, 1969-1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1970-1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1970s (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Carl Solway Gallery, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Columbus Museum of Art, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - E.P. Gurewitsch Works of Art, Inc., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Gimpel Fils, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Guggenheim Museum, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Hirschl and Adler Modern, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Linssen Gallery, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Maxwell Davidson Gallery, 1980-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Moving Blade (1964), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - New York State Award to Kenan Center, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - New York State Governor's Art Award, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Outdoors: Fordham University Plaza at Lincoln Center" (1975) (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Skowhegan Medals, 1973-1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Staempfli Gallery, 1964-1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Unstable Axis (1970), 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Zabriskie Gallery, 1967-1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1968-1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Robinson, Boardman, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Rogalski, Walter, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Rogers, John, 1976-1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Ronnebeck, Arnold, circa 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Rosati, James (Box 20)
    - General, 1970-1981 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - A. Richard Denatale, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Big Red (1971), 1971-1987 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Construction (1968), circa 1970 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Death of the Artist, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Lippincott II (1962), 1970-1989 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Lippincott, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1970-1984 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - National Gallery of Art, circa 1980s (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Study for Necropolis (1968), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Untitled (1965), Crayon Drawing, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Untitled (1969), Crayon Drawing, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Untitled (1967), Three Crayon Drawings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Yale University Art Gallery, 1970-1978 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Samaras, Lucas, 1968-1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Sanso, Juvenal, 1964-1974 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Schanker, Louis, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Schlemmer, Oskar, 1969-1987 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Seager, Harry, 1964-1978 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Segal, George (Box 20)
    - General, 1968-1988 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1968-1992 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Articles Regarding Richard Serra's Tilted Arc, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Election to American Academy-Institute of Arts and Letters, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Gay Liberation (1980), 1979-1984 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - George Segal, Book by Sam Hunter and Don Hawthorne, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Girl in a Chair (1968), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - The Holocaust, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Judge at 36th Western New York Exhibition, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Letter Regarding Penney's Visit to Artist's Studio, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Nina Freudenheim Gallery, 1976-1984 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Post Cards, circa 1970s (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Periodical, Saturday Review, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - The Restaurant (1977), 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Sidney Janis Gallery, 1967-1986 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Sistine Chapel Restoration, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Toll Booth (1980) at Newark Museum (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Woman Brushing Her Hair (1964), Serigraph from New York Ten Portfolio, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Shinn, Everett (Box 20)
    - General, 1960-1992 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Country Street, circa 1980s (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Graham Gallery, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Jordan-Volpe Gallery, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Mary Wollstonecraft, 1962-1993 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Simpson, Lewis C., 1965-1973 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Sloan, John (Box 20)
    - General, 1970-1987 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Associated American Artists, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Berry-Hill Galleries, Inc., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Chamisa (circa 1922), 1962-1980 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - "Focus I: John Sloan, The Wake of the Ferry, II" (1984) (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - "The Gloucester Years" (1982) at Grace Borgenicht Gallery (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Hull Gallery, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Indian Detour (1927), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - "John Sloan 1871-1951" (1971) (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - "John Sloan, The Gloucester Years" (1980-1981) (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - "John Sloan Memorial, His Complete Graphic Work" (1956), 1956-1964 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Sloan, John (Box 21)
    - "John Sloan: Paintings, Prints, Drawings" (1982-1983) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "John Sloan: Paintings from the Ruth Martin Collection" (1980), 1980-1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "John Sloan: Spectator of Life" (1988) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1964-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Kraushaar Galleries, 1965-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Material Regarding Books About the Artist, 1965-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The Wake of the Ferry (1949), Painting on 8-Cent Stamp, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1971-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Smith, David (Box 21)
    - General, 1957-1992 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
    - Big Diamond (1952), 1967-1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Dorothy Dehner, Wife, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - "Drawings with Color" (1980) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Material Regarding Drawings, 1979-1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - M. Knoedler and Co., 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Untitled (1934), Drawing, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Tony (Box 21)
    - General, 1971-1981 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, circa 1990s (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Death of the Artist, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - M. Knoedler and Co., 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Pace Gallery, 1979-1983 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Paula Cooper Gallery, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Playground (1965), 1970-1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Spitball (1961), 1970-1992 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Xavier Fourcade, Inc., 1976-1987 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Soffer, Sasson, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Sonoyama, Harumi, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Soulages, Pierre, 1964-1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Soyer, Raphael, General, 1967-1988 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Soyer, Raphael, Associated American Artists, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Spaventa, George, 1979-1989 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Stamos, Theodoros (Box 21)
    - General, 1966-1994 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - ACA Galleries, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1962-1970 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Art Students League, 1963-1987 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1960 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Camillos Kouros Gallery, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Dorsky Gallery, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Ericson Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - G Contemporary Paintings, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Harcourts Contemporary, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Judge at Western New York Annual Exhibition, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Letters Regarding Katherine Kuh and Charmion Von Weigand, 1982-1989 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Louis K. Meisel Gallery, 1978-1993 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Marathon (1971), 1962-1989 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Mark Rothko Estate, 1972-1986 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Solomon and Co., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, circa 1966 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Steinberg, Saul (Box 21)
    - General, 1969-1982 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Albergo Minerva (1965), General, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Albergo Minerva (1965) in Retrospective Exhibitions, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Articles About the Artist, 1969-1978 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Cartoons, 1966-1979 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Guild Hall Award, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Hedda Sterne, Ex-Wife, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - The Inspector (1973) (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - The New Yorker Magazine Covers, 1975-1980 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Pace Gallery, 1982-1989 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Periodical, Time Magazine, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Post Cards, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Posters, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - "Saul Steinberg: Drawings and Watercolors from Hallmark Collection" (1984) (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Speech (1955), 1969 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - "Steinberg at the Smithsonian: The Metamorphoses of an Emblem" (1973-1974) (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Stella, Frank, 1966-1990 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Stella, Frank, 1966-1990 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Stella, Joseph, 1963-1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Storrs, John (Box 22)
    - General, 1965-1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Archives of American Art, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Death Bed Portrait of Rodin (1917), 1973-1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Retrospective Exhibition at Whitney Museum of American Art (1986-1987) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1972-1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Self Portrait (1918), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Suba, Miklos, 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Summers, Carol, 1980-1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Swann, Don, 1966-1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Takal, Peter, 1964-1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Taylor, James Earl, 1970-1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Tilson, Joe, 1966-1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Tobey, Marc, 1970-1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Trova, Ernest (Box 22)
    - General, 1966-1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - ACA Galleries, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Manscape (1967), 1968-1985 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Vasarely, Victor, 1966-1984 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Von Wiegand, Charmion, 1964-1993 (Box 22, Folder 21)